♪ It seems today that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those good
old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Ah, the water park.
Happy anniversary, Lois.
Everybody meet back here in six hours.
I can't wait to get everyone else's
body water in my mouth.
Uh, where's the slide?
Just eat this Starburst.
Wow, lemons, oranges, cherries.
So juicy!
I don't think that was a Starburst.
I think that may have just been acid.
Would you like to ride the
Skittles rainbow now?
Is it also acid?
My friend, I'm an adult who
works at a water park.
If I give you something, it's acid.
No going down headfirst,
and wait till I say it's okay.
Go. Go. Go.
Hey!
I'm gaining on you, Brian.
Meg, slow down.
You're coming way too fast.
Ew, Brian, what happened?
I don't know.
Hey, idiot,
you got to wait till the guy says go.
Excuse me, do you think
you can help me out?
Sure, just let me do
an awkward, extremely
unattractive pool walk over to you.
Hey, what's up?
My top came off on the slide.
I think I may have seen you
put it in your shorts.
Okay, well, here's my shorts.
Just fish out the one that's yours.
Thank you so much.
I'm Isabella.
I'm Chris.
Listen, my aunt is waiting for me,
but it was nice to meet you, Chris.
You, too.
Enjoy the boobs of your morning.
Afternoon!
Enjoy the boobs of your afternoon.
My word, Chris, that girl
was totally into you.
You should ask her out.
Really? But what if she says no?
Hey, if you want something,
you've got to go for it.
Just like the fat man did
when he changed his name.
I'm looking for a Peter Ferrari.
Obviously, that's me.
Yes, there's a soiled
pair of Ferrari underwear
in the men's room trash.
Who took 'em out of the sink?
They were soaking.
Sir, I can't park this.
There's diarrhea all over the front seat
of your PT Cruiser.
Isabella, listen, I'm not great at this,
but...
Told you.
Also, I was wondering
if there's any chance
you'd maybe want to go
out with me sometime.
Oh, Chris, that's sweet,
but I don't think you'd
want to go out with me.
- Why not?
- It's just that, well, I have kids.
Oh, wow. And a couple of cuties.
We got any teeth coming in?
Oh, oh, I think I feel something.
Please, please don't do that.
Hey, your aunt is
Consuela? Hi, Consuela.
- You two know each other?
- Oh, yeah.
"Lemon Pledge," "No,
no." All that stuff.
Is time to go.
Lemon Pledge, no, no.
See?
But wait, Isabella,
I don't care that you have kids.
I'd still like to go out with you.
Wow, that's really sweet, Chris.
Okay, you're on.
Here's my number.
Oh, boy, I haven't been this excited
since our trip to Philadelphia.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Flight 427 to Philadelphia
has been canceled.
Yay!
I saw Lady and the Tramp,
so I asked if we could
eat spaghetti in the
alley, but they said no,
because of all the
homeless masturbation.
Oh, I love that movie.
Chris, I'm having a really
nice time with you.
You are? Listen, this is probably lame,
but I learned a little
bit of your language,
and I just wanted to say...
_
What language is that?
You're Korean, are you not?
No, I'm Mexican.
_
Hey, Chris. Where are you off to?
Oh, Isabella's coming by,
and we're gonna take
the kids to the park.
Wow, you two are spending
a lot of time together.
Uh, are you sure you want to date a girl
who's... had so much experience?
What do you mean?
Like, maybe she's got some city miles
on her voo-voo.
Not to mention a couple of blowouts.
- Hey, Bri...
- Yup, I heard you.
She's talking about her kids, Chris.
Oh, I don't care about that, Mom.
I just want to make sure you're
not getting in over your head.
Well, I'm sure someone's
already been in there
deeper than that, Lois.
Brian.
Oh, hello, Isabella.
Hi, Mrs. Griffin, Mr. Griffin.
Mr. Griffin's up here, sweetheart.
Well, I guess you two have fun.
Okay, bye.
Look, I can see why you're concerned
that Chris' girlfriend has kids,
but he's happy, and she
seems like she's into him.
Plus, she's... she's hot.
Yeah, she is.
I bit my lip off.
Go away, Mr. Herbert!
It's not me.
I'm in your closet.
Isabella.
Is everything okay?
Chris, I just wanted to say good-bye.
Wha-What do you mean?
I found out that I'm
going to be deported.
They're sending me back
to Mexico in the morning.
So, in other words,
this could have waited
till the morning?
I didn't want to leave
without saying good-bye.
But they can't send you away.
There's got to be something we can do.
Unfortunately, there's not.
But don't worry, I'm planning on
getting back into the
country as soon as I can.
What are you gonna do,
just leave the babies with Consuela?
I wish I could, but she
works seven days a week,
between housekeeping
and being the new CEO of Yahoo.
Maybe we should improve
our business model.
No, no.
Improve our original content?
So we have no corporate identity?
We secondary e-mail people use
to sign up for porn sites.
So, are you taking your
boys back with you?
I guess I have no choice.
But I hate having to.
The whole reason I left Mexico
was to give them a better life.
Well, I could take them
until you get back.
I mean, I'm no expert
at this sort of thing,
but...
Wow, you're getting better at that.
But I can't ask you to
take care of my children.
Isabella, I want to do this.
Chris, stop.
You would really look
after my kids for me?
Of course I would.
You're a wonderful man, Chris Griffin.
Thank you. Gracias.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
Don't worry, I'm gonna
take good care of you.
I'm gonna call you "Juan,"
and I'm gonna call you "Two."
Good, he's been reading the book.
Uh, Dad, you're reading
the paper upside down.
Wrong again, idiot.
Chris, what are you doing
with Isabella's babies?
And why are you holding them that way?
You'll hurt them. Where's Isabella?
She got deported this morning.
Deported? A-And she just
left her babies with you?
Well, just until she can come back.
Chris, are you crazy?
What makes you think you can
take care of two babies?
I don't know, I've seen
her take care of them.
I see you with Stewie.
Frankly, it doesn't seem that hard.
You just shattered her world.
Shattered.
Absolutely not, Chris.
I will not allow this.
Look, I made a promise to Isabella,
and I'm gonna keep it.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
these two need to eat.
He bought a breast-feeding book.
Someone may want to pop in on him.
There's no way Chris is
gonna be able to take care
of two babies.
Well, maybe he should
have thought of that
before he opened his slut legs.
No, Peter, that's not...
Anyway, we got to call Child Services.
Lois, if you do that,
Chris will resent you
for the rest of his life.
Then what do you suggest we do?
I say you let him try.
Trust me, one day of
watching those kids,
and he'll want them out of here.
All right, fine.
Yes, taking care of
kids is a 24-hour job.
Like when I worked at
that all-night diner
from that painting.
They kicked me out of the
war for kissing a guy.
All right, guys, nothing
but the best for you two,
so I got you all-organic,
non-GMO, no-hormone food.
That'll be $500.
Ah, well, sorry, kids.
Looks like we're gonna
go to Jersey Mike's
and hope that future
science will save us.
Yay, we're jar people!
Ah! Science, help!
Jersey Mike's.
Bring your girlfriend
with the fat ass in here.
Hey, guys, how about a little TV?
We can watch a baby thing together.
Baby Einstein, Muppet Babies.
Uh, what's CSI: Babies?
What's this?
They can't solve this crime,
they're just frightened babies.
They don't even know it's a crime,
they just know their
parents aren't there.
They're scared, now I'm
scared. Turn this off!
Aah, that's not what I want!
Aah, I'm gonna go hide in my couch fort!
Is CSI: Babies over yet?
Oh, hello, Consuela.
You must be here for the twins.
No, no take babies.
I have good news and ay, ay, ay news.
Okay, give us the ay, ay, ay news first.
Isabella no can come back.
Stuck in Mexico.
The babies, they stay here.
What?!
What's the good news?
Good news is bus get new wiper blades.
No more "ee-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa."
"Ee-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa."
Well, these kids are not staying here.
You got to take them.
How can I take them...
when I was never here?
Wow, she's like the
Mexican David Blaine.
Wait, is David Blaine Mexican?
He's something.
Peter, forget that.
What are we gonna do?
Chris can't just be stuck
with these babies.
Why not?
I'm doing a great job.
I love Isabella and I love her kids.
Chris, you're living in a dreamland.
How are you gonna support two babies?
I could just take some time
off school and get a job.
No, absolutely not.
Well, now-now hold on, Lois, hold on,
maybe Chris getting a
job's not the worst idea.
I mean, I made pretty good money
when I hosted that confusing game show.
All right, Phil, come stand
by me, it's Ashley's turn.
Ashley, go ahead, pick an
answer, find a question,
spin the table, and remember,
the clock is ticking backwards.
I'll pass?
Congrats, you win.
Sorry to see you go.
And, Phil, we'll see you tomorrow.
Well, that's all the time we have.
For those of you playing at home, why?
And how?
Audience?
Why... and... how!
Stop that!
Forget it, I will not allow
you to drop out of school.
If Isabella can't get here
to take her kids back,
we'll just have to bring them to her.
What? What do you mean?
I mean we're going to Mexico
so we can give these kids
back to their mother.
Peter, back me up here.
♪ Let's get those kids
back to their mama. ♪
Look how winded he is
from doing that one spin.
Your
mother's right, Chris.
We're going to Mexico.
Oh.
I got to sit.
All right, we're off to Mexico.
If you kids are good,
we'll bring you back
a tangled marionette.
Is it gonna be a long trip, Dad?
No, not too bad.
Especially since we're gonna do
it to the wrong stock footage.
Boy, what a trip.
Chris, are you sure this
is Isabella's village?
This place looks pretty rough.
Yeah, this is it.
Santa Terrible.
Look, there she is!
Chris!
What in the Mind of Mencia
are you doing here?
My babies!
Isabella, I missed you so much.
Ay, Chris, I missed you, too.
Look, Isabella, you shouldn't be
separated from your children,
so we've brought them to you.
We wish you all the best.
Say good-bye, Chris.
Mom, we can't just leave them here.
This is no place for
Isabella to raise a family.
Oh, you're right, Chris.
I didn't want you to have to
raise those babies yourself.
But as a mom, I don't know
if I can in good conscience
leave this family here.
We'll just have to smuggle
her and her babies back in.
Well, no one's better at
smuggling than El Chapo.
Maybe he can help us.
How are you gonna get El Chapo to help?
It's easy.
All you got to do is say
"dyed black eyebrows"
into the wind, and he appears.
Dyed black eyebrows.
Can I help you?
Peter Gallagher?
Maybe I can help.
Mark Cuban?
Oh, we're getting all
the wrong eyebrow guys.
Mrs. Griffin, you would take the risk
of smuggling me and my
children across the border?
But you could be arrested.
I realize that, but you
have just as much right
to a decent life for your
children as anyone else.
Now we just need a plan.
All right, what if we...
run!
Damn it, Peter!
What about Quagmire?
He could probably get
his hands on a plane.
Lois, that's actually a great idea.
"Actually"?
W-Why are you saying it like that?
And Quagmire owes me a
favor anyway, remember?
Last time he went out of town,
I sat on his eggs for him.
Peter, it's time for lunch.
Sorry, Lois, can't leave the
eggs till Quagmire gets back.
We're having sloppy joes.
Well, I guess I haven't seen
that mongoose in a while.
We're having sloppy joes.
Yeah, I heard.
Please say you got the onion bun...
We're having sloppy joes.
Mongoose!
Mongeese!
Hey, just a heads-up, my
dad's friend, Mr. Quagmire,
is gonna say a lot of stuff to you,
and it's all gonna be disgusting.
Hey, you must be Isabella.
I came as soon as I heard about you.
And then I got on my plane.
All right.
Hold it right there!
Uh-oh. Somebody's coming.
N-Now, hold on, hold on.
I put my business card in a
fishbowl at an El Torito.
This could be about that.
Polic├нa! Put your hands up!
Is this about the raffle
for the free lunch?
Does it have to be during
the week, because I...
Aah!
Wait a second, are we being arrested?
We've done nothing wrong.
We're not arresting you.
We're taking your plane.
And, Javier, get their
keys and take their SUV.
Ah, that stupid, fat guido.
No, Peter, that's the wrong racial slur.
No, I know, I was just
thinking about Snooki.
Boy, I can't believe there'd
be corrupt cops in Mexico.
Yeah, Donald Trump was right:
his daughter is a hot piece of ass.
Uh, you guys, don't panic,
but there's a couple
of coyotes over there.
Oh, like Coyote Ugly with Piper Perabo.
Peh... I-is that it?
Peh-Peh-ree... Peh-ree-bow?
Peh-Pera... Pera-Pera-boo?
Pera-boo? Say it with me.
Per-Per-a-bow.
Is that right?
It's weird, but you remember.
You know? I guess...
I guess that's the point.
Do you think she's set for life?
Peter, we're about to die!
No, my babies!
Get out of here!
You leave them alone!
Ow!
Ah! Chris!
You guys, I've been bit!
And it got away with my
friendship bracelet.
You are a boy.
Chris, you saved my babies.
Oh, my God, Peter, we did nothing.
We're his parents and we did nothing.
I know, but, wow,
did you see how Chris
took care of those kids?
Up till now, the only thing
he could take care of
was my traffic tickets.
- Name?
- Uh, Peter Griffin.
Peter Griffin's here to surrender
for his vehicular manslaughter.
What? No.
I'm a good boy!
He is a good boy.
Oh, this is awful.
Chris is injured,
and we're completely
out of food and water.
I know.
I'm so thirsty, I'd be willing
to drink anyone's pee.
Not-Not yours, Chris or Peter.
But, you know, you know, anyone.
Mom, Dad, thanks for trying to help.
You know, I just wanted
to do the right thing,
but now we're all gonna die.
Did-Did you gals hear my pee thing?
Time for clean getaway.
- Consuela?
- ┬┐T├нa?
Ay, thank God.
How did you find us?
Babies' earring have chip.
Oh, well, this is great.
Can you help us get to the border?
Oh, you already in United States.
We are?
Yes, this Texas.
What?
S-So, wait, so we walked
right across the border
and didn't even know it?
That is a problem.
Right?
I mean, politics aside,
we can all agree,
that is a problem.
Thanks for the ride, Consuela.
And thanks for talking us on
that little detour to Dollywood.
Was I right, or was I right?
Yep, totally worth the extra two days.
Look, Chris, I owe you an apology.
I didn't believe in you.
I was wrong to say you couldn't
handle the responsibility
of taking care of two kids.
Y-You risked your life for those babies.
Well, I didn't want them to get hurt.
That's right.
Because you care about them,
just like you care about Isabella.
And if you want to continue to date her
and be a part of those kids' lives,
I'd be just fine with that.
Are you kidding? Screw that.
Looking after babies is a nightmare.
Oh, you have no idea.
You know how many times I
had you kids in the oven,
just daring myself to turn it on?
Well, thanks for trusting me
to figure it out for myself.
I love you, Mom.
I love you, too, sweetheart.
Isabella, being with you
has been really great.
But I think I realized my mom was right.
I'm too young to be taking
on this much responsibility.
I understand.
But I know someday you will
make an incredible father.
Good-bye, Chris.
Good-bye, Isabella.
Chris, time for dinner.
We're having sloppy joes.
Oh, boy!
Yeah, I heard you.
Oh, dear God.
Oh, they're all dead.
No, please, no!
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru
We're having sloppy joes.